Create a focus area dashboard 2: Learning Aspirations of Genz Dashboard 
1. Decide your primary KPI on your his dashboard and include it at the top 
2. Decide your Secondary KPI on your for this dashboard and include it at the top 
3. Make Gender as a Slicer for all the charts 
4. Create a bar chart to visualize the most preferred working environment among respondents. 
5. Create a histogram chart to show which career category is most preferred among respondents. 
6. Create a bar chart to display the percentage of respondents who prefer fully remote work. 
7. Create a bar chart to show the distribution of respondents based on the frequency of office visits in a hybrid working environment. 
8. Create a stacked bar chart to compare the percentage of respondents aspiring for specific careers with those considering higher education abroad as an alternative. 


Create a focus area dashboard 2: Manager Aspirations of Genz Dashboard 
1. Decide your primary KPI on your for this dashboard and include them at the top 
2. Decide your Secondary KPI on your for this dashboard and include them at the top 
3. Make Gender as a Slicer for all the charts 
4. Bar chart: How do respondents feel about working for one employer for 3 years or more? 
5. Stacked bar chart: How does the team size preference relate to the preferred employers? 
6. Histogram Chart: Are there any noticeable patterns in the distribution of responses for each manager type? 
7. Horizontal Bar Chart: Which employer qualities are most preferred by employees, and can we visualize this preference? 
8. Bar Chart: Which team size has the highest number of employees who are willing to work for one employer for 7 years or more? 
9. Stacked Bar Chart: Do employees who prefer a certain type of manager also tend to prefer specific employers? (Analyze whether there are patterns between manager preferences and employer preferences.) 


Create a focus area dashboard 1: Mission Aspirations of Genz Dashboard 
1. How many Genz Would You Work for a Company with an Undefined Mission? ( make as KPI ) 
2. How many Genz would you work for a company whose mission is misaligned with their public actions or even their product? ( make as KPI ) 
3. Make Gender as the Slicer for all the charts
4. Stacked bar chart: How does the likelihood of "MisalignedMissionLikelihood" vary among respondents? 
5. Histogram chart: What is the distribution of the "NoSocialImpactLikelihood" scores? 
6. Clustered bar chart or a grouped bar chart: How does the likelihood of "MisalignedMissionLikelihood" vary with different expected salary ranges in 3 years? 
7. Bar chart: What are the top three most common expected salary ranges for respondents in 3 years? 
8. Pie chart: What is the distribution of responses for "MissionUndefinedLikelihood" (yes/no)? 
9. Line chart: How does the likelihood of "NoSocialImpactLikelihood" change based on the number of laid-off employees? (A line chart to illustrate how "NoSocialImpactLikelihood" varies with different levels of laid-off employees, if applicable.) 

Note: You have to add histogram charts in the Power BI. So the below link to how to enable the histogram charts. https://youtu.be/ashxc_escL4?si=gRz7_Y14yoaEQ-K7 


